All right. And here's the solution. To start off, let's
look at our forecast fragment query. Since it's a join
between two tables, it's really easy for us to add
additional parameters to our query. Now we make sure we keep
the column indices consistent. Now we've grabbed the latitude and
longitude at the same time we're grabbing our weather entries.
The next thing to do is to move the function
open preferred location in map over to forecast fragment. Instead of
using shared preferences to get these values, we can actually
get the cursor from the forecast adapter. We can get
our cursor moved to a reasonable position, and then build
our new string which is just latitude colon longitude. We'll
leave our comment where it was. Finally, we just have
to fix up a few things in the code and
that's it. Well, at least for the code. We still
need to do some work in XML. Let's move this R.ID.action
map now over to forecast fragment inside of it on
options item selected. And now we've got to do some
XML work. Let's look at our main menu. We'll just
pull this action map item out, and we'll place it right
into forecast fragment. All right. One more thing to do
while we're here. One of the things Raito talked about was
wanting to get rid of the refresh menu item. So,
let's just comment it out. When we remove that action refresh
item, we should probably comment it out from our source
code too. After all, you never know when you'll want to
use that for debugging. So, there we have it. Our
final app. No longer having a refresh button. With a
new exciting setting to turn off and on weather notifications.
Details are taken care of. I hope you've enjoyed building
Sunshine. There's still lots of things left to do in
Sunshine. For example, we could also add a lot more intelligent
things to its user interface. And of course, we
could make it a lot smarter about synching data.
And I hope the practices you've learned building Sunshine
will help you in all of your future applications